In all these years of experience at
Lamborghini, what is the most
difficult moment?   There have been quite a
few [musical ones], I must
say.  One was when the crisis hit
in 20080,
because we had to decide how much to slow down
production and at the same time it was
also a time of
significant investments because the
2011 sales were coming. This was a
very, very difficult period and then the
difficult period was naturally
the whole period after [music] Covid
because on the one hand we had to reinvest
in new products, we had to decide
which was the right product, [music]
whether combustion, hybrid or electric.  And
of course now first with the war
in Ukraine, then with the tariffs, the
Chinese market that has collapsed for luxury cars
and now also the crisis in the
Middle East in which [music] there is no
longer a stable basis to rely on.
And once you made a bet
that others said maybe be careful, you did it
anyway,
maybe it worked even to overcome these
moments.  The challenge is to do things
and then keep doing them until you
achieve them, without having to change your
dreams every moment.  This is
important, isn't it?  Staying on
course even when others doubt,
especially in dark times,
when there is a crisis or when
technology needs to change.  This is
important.
And what is the baradetta?  What are the things
that need to be respected?  When you start a
journey, you follow it through to the end.
Sulibrio.  There have been many moments
where we have had imbalances or
moments where we thought it wouldn't
work.  That's our idea of
focusing on something that
really changes the brand.